[{"answer": "As president of the United States, I'll have your back.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "Can it take him all the way?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "Mitt Romney's ugly attacks are going to backfire.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 15, "question": "What does he say about ads like this?", "qSentId": 14}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "Because a lot rests on that, I would imagine, in terms of where the investigation goes, in terms of which doctor she was seeing, which prescriptions, what drugs she was actually taking?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "That the drugs that they found in her hotel room should not be mixed with alcohol, right?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "TEINBERG: I don't think it's unique to Los Angeles.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "Is it unique to Los Angeles and the way that that is allowed to happen?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Well, it depends on a lot of things.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Would it be negligent for a doctor to prescribe Whitney Houston with the kind of prescription drugs she had if they knew her to be an addict?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "You know, my reaction was I took to my Twitter account and I said, what's scummy about the music industry is that everybody loves you when you're dead.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "What was your reaction when you heard that Whitney Houston had died?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "I mean what's been a common theme throughout the week from the guests I've had is those who knew Whitney Houston saying she was very strong-willed.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "At what point do we lose the courage and we started letting the other people run our lives?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "I, too, am very strong-willed.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "What would you say to that argument?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "It has been, at times --", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Is it pills?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "OUSTON: At times.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "All?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "That would be me.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "If you had to name the devil, for you, the biggest devil among them?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "You know, I'm in a unique situation there where I actually never had a rock doc as they call them.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "How easy has it been over the years for you to get pretty much any drug you like?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "You know I don't really understand how it works.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "How do these rock docs go about their business?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "And Piers, can I ask you a question?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "Well, this to me comes to the absolute crux of this, because you know, it's not like we are best friends or I know you that well, but I do know that you are a recovering addict.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "If I went to your house for dinner and you know I'm a recovering alcoholic, and I ask for a glass of wine with dinner, what would you say?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "I think that is the key question.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "How can we hold them accountable?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "Well, it's a program of action sobriety, Piers.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Why don't you think she wanted to get sober?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, it's twofold.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "What's your reaction to that as a former addict?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "Very engaging.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "What was -- how did you find her?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "All this, if you were genuinely concerned about her, wouldn't you do something to stop this?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "Well, both of those.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Or in the end, did it have to come from within?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "It was that interview with Karen and the kids that launched this, Piers.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "You must be enjoying yourself, aren't you?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "Well, the establishment has always been for Romney.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "How do you explain that?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "Oh, no.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Do you think that Newt Gingrich should pull out now, as some people are suggesting today?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Cumulatively, just off the top of my head, it's probably a little -- over three million dollars in those four years.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "And how much money have you earned in those four years?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "No, I feel -- look, I feel very blessed.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "So pretty successful?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "Well, all my income is earned income.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "How do you think the way the public will react to that?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Well, I have been very blessed.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "How would you summarize them?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "Well, that's the Catholic Church's position, period, that it's wrong.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "Is that what your position on this?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, you know, you see this problem on the -- on the screen, where folks who are very famous -- as you know, in your own country, you go back into the examples of the aristocracy and the impact on the rest of society throughout the history of Britain, and vice versa, when -- when the aristocracy changed their behavior.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "Well, it shouldn't be accepted practice.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "There should be some more controlled regulation of this, to stop this sort of accepted practice over there, where you can almost go to 20 doctors if you want to?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Where did that voice come from?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "So the whole family sings?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "ESTMAN: She has a rich voice.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "I know that she was something special to you, right?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "I was heart broken.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "How did you feel when you heard that she had died?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "I actually was, yeah.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "Were you watching the Grammys?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "I mean, it appeared unexpectedly.", "docId": "120215pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "And when you saw yourself coming up on a bus singing like Adele, what did you think?", "qSentId": 581}]